protectamerica.com 2012-06-23

# Privacy Policy | Security Systems | Alarm Monitoring | Protect America

## Protect America, Inc. Privacy Policy (www.protectamerica.com)

**Effective:** May 17, 2005

**Last Updated:** February 10, 2009

[Protect America](http://www.protectamerica.com/ "Protect America Home | www.protectamerica.com"), Inc. is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to us. In particular, we believe it is important for you to know how we treat information about you that we may receive from this Web site.

## Information Collected

In general, you can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. Our web servers also seek (as many Web sites do) to place a "cookie" (a small data file) on your computer's hard drive. This allows the server to determine the computer when it visits again. We use this information in order to track statistical information about navigation to and throughout certain areas of our site, and to PAI promotions on other sites. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. This cookie is not used to obtain your name or any personal data, and the information that is tracked is used only for internal purposes, such as to improve site navigation and to measure the effectiveness of our promotional placements, and is not shared with anyone other than PAI affiliates and contractors who assist PAI in these efforts and are bound to confidentiality. However, if you prefer not to accept cookies, you can set your browser to reject them or to alert you before one is placed.

In addition, there are portions of this Web site where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information you request. The information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address.

We use a third-party technology to place our advertisements on other Web sites. This technology will install a small "cookie" file on your computer when you view our ad. These cookies will not contain any information that personally identifies you (such as your name or e-mail address) but they will contain a randomly generated number that is unique to your browser and can be recognized by a "Web beacon" (transparent GIF file) on our site if you click through to our site from one of our ads. This allows us to keep track of how many unique visitors we have to our site and from what ads they entered, so that we can measure the effectiveness of our ads and ad placements. The privacy policies of the Web sites on which we advertise, and through which the cookies are installed should inform you about the cookie, and you may of course set your browser to reject cookies. To learn more about the third-party ad-serving technology that we use, cookies, and how to "opt-out," please [email us](http://www.protectamerica.com/pa/info@protectamerica.com "Protect America | Email: Information").

This Web site is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children.

## Security of Collected Information

We maintain strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. We restrict access to information about you to those PAI workers who need to know the information to respond to your inquiry or request. Workers who misuse personal information are subject to disciplinary action.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ssl>.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [webmaster@protectamerica.com](mailto:webmaster@protectamerica.com "Protect America | Email: Webmaster").

## Phone Call Information

If you call a telephone number listed on our Web site, we may collect Personal Information from you, including your name and telephone number through caller identification and reverse call technology. We also may record the telephone conversation. We record the telephone conversation to track the performance of our advertisements and for quality assurance purposes. We do not record the calls for the purpose of collecting your Personal Information. If we record the telephone conversation, we will notify you before the conversation begins. In addition to ProtectAmerica.com, the only parties that have access to the recording are the telephone service provider and ProtectAmerica.com contractors and affiliates who assist strictly in the efforts described in this paragraph, and who are bound by confidentiality.

I am genuinely interested in a GE Security System to protect my home and family. By providing my contact information and telephone number, I expressly authorize ProtectAmerica.com or their affiliates to contact me at the telephone number that I have provided and/or the email address that I have provided in respect to this offer and any new offers made available in the future, even though I may have previously chosen to have the telephone number that I provided or the email address that I provided added to any Do-Not-Call List or anti-spam list including the lists maintained by ProtectAmerica.com or their affiliates or any local, state, or federal government agency. I further acknowledge that by submitting this request, ProtectAmerica.com or their affiliates have my permission to contact me via telephone and/or email.

## Use of Collected Information

By submitting a request form on any of the Protect America, Inc web properties or online offers, I authorize Protect America, Inc. or their affiliates to contact me by telephone and/or email in respect to this offer and any new offers made available in the future.

Domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site.

When other information is collected from you, such as your name and e-mail address, we let you know at the time of collection how we will use the personal information. We use the personal information you provide only to respond to your inquiry or to process your request (such as to receive information about our products and services). This information may be shared with other PAI businesses, but only if necessary to fulfill your request or for related purposes.

We may share the personal information you provide with other companies or affiliates. These companies are contractually bound to use personal information we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide. PAI utilizes the services and securely shares the appropriate information with the major credit bureaus, credit card processors and shipping companies. We do not share, sell, or lease personal information about you to any outside third-parties for their marketing use. We will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are required by law to do so and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, or in other legally limited circumstances (for example, to protect your account from fraud).

If you register with one of PAI's affiliates online, they may use this information to provide you with custom information about PAI's offerings in support of your business needs. They may also seek to place a "cookie" (small data file) as discussed above in order to provide you with tailored information. You should review the privacy policy associated with their web site for further information about their privacy practices.

[

## Tell-A-Friend

](http://www.protectamerica.com/pa/cust_ref "Protect America | Tell-A-Friend Referral Service")

If you choose to use our [referral service](http://www.protectamerica.com/pa/cust_ref "Protect America | Tell-A-Friend Referral Service") to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. PAI does not store this information. The information is used only for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

## Access to Personally Identifiable Information and Choice/Opt-out

If you purchase a product/service or request more information on our products/services but do not wish to receive any additional marketing materials from PAI you may "opt-out" on our [unsubscribe page](http://www.protectamerica.com/unsubscribe.htm "Unsubscribe from E-mails from Protect America"). If your personally identifiable information changes you make the change by emailing our Customer Support at [support@protectamerica.com](mailto:support@protectamerica.com "Protect America | Email: Support"), by contacting us by telephone: 1.800.951.5111 or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

## Links to Other Sites

PAI's Web site may contain links to other sites such as PAI distributors and affiliates. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites.

## Changes in this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we decide to make material changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

## TRUSTe Program

PAI is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site http://www.protectamerica.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact the Webmaster at [webmaster@protectamerica.com](mailto:webmaster@protectamerica.com "Protect America | Email: Webmaster"). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at [TRUSTe Watchdog](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php "TRUSTe Watchdog"). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

[

## Contacting Us

](http://www.protectamerica.com/pa/contact "Protect America | Contact Information")

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please [email us](mailto:info@protectamerica.com "Email Protect America Information Inbox"). We welcome your questions and suggestions about our privacy policy.

[

## Protect America, Inc.

](http://www.protectamerica.com/pa/map "Map to Protect America, Inc.")

3800 Quick Hill Rd. Building 1-100  
Austin, TX 78728 

## Call us today toll-free at

1.800.951.5111  
or e-mail us at  

  *[PAI]: Protect America, Inc.
